export var data = [
    {
      name: "Object1",
      answer: "Answer for Object1",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "What is the first question for Object1?",
          answer: "Answer 1 for Object1",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object1?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object1",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object1?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object1",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object1?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object1",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          question: "What is the second question for Object1?",
          answer: "Answer 2 for Object1",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object1?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object1",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object1?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object1",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object1?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object1",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          question: "What is the third question for Object1?",
          answer: "Answer 3 for Object1",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object1?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object1",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object1?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object1",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object1?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object1",
            },
          ],
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      name: "Object2",
      answer: "Answer for Object2",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "What is the first question for Object2?",
          answer: "Answer 1 for Object2",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object2?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object2",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object2?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object2",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object2?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object2",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          question: "What is the second question for Object2?",
          answer: "Answer 2 for Object2",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object2?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object2",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object2?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object2",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object2?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object2",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          question: "What is the third question for Object2?",
          answer: "Answer 3 for Object2",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object2?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object2",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object2?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object2",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object2?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object2",
            },
          ],
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      name: "Object3",
      answer: "Answer for Object3",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "What is the first question for Object3?",
          answer: "Answer 1 for Object3",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object3?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object3",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object3?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object3",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object3?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object3",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          question: "What is the second question for Object3?",
          answer: "Answer 2 for Object3",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object3?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object3",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object3?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object3",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object3?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object3",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          question: "What is the third question for Object3?",
          answer: "Answer 3 for Object3",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object3?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object3",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object3?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object3",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object3?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object3",
            },
          ],
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      name: "Object4",
      answer: "Answer for Object4",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "What is the first question for Object4?",
          answer: "Answer 1 for Object4",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object4?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object4",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object4?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object4",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object4?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object4",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          question: "What is the second question for Object4?",
          answer: "Answer 2 for Object4",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object4?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object4",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object4?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object4",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object4?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object4",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          question: "What is the third question for Object4?",
          answer: "Answer 3 for Object4",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object4?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object4",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object4?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object4",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object4?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object4",
            },
          ],
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      name: "Object5",
      answer: "Answer for Object5",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "What is the first question for Object5?",
          answer: "Answer 1 for Object5",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object5?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object5",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object5?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object5",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object5?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object5",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          question: "What is the second question for Object5?",
          answer: "Answer 2 for Object5",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object5?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object5",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object5?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object5",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object5?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object5",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          question: "What is the third question for Object5?",
          answer: "Answer 3 for Object5",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object5?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object5",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object5?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object5",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object5?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object5",
            },
          ],
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      name: "Object6",
      answer: "Answer for Object6",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "What is the first question for Object6?",
          answer: "Answer 1 for Object6",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object6?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object6",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object6?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object6",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object6?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object6",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          question: "What is the second question for Object6?",
          answer: "Answer 2 for Object6",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object6?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object6",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object6?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object6",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object6?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object6",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          question: "What is the third question for Object6?",
          answer: "Answer 3 for Object6",
          subQuestions: [
            {
              question: "What is the first sub-question for Object6?",
              answer: "Answer 1 for Object6",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the second sub-question for Object6?",
              answer: "Answer 2 for Object6",
            },
            {
              question: "What is the third sub-question for Object6?",
              answer: "Answer 3 for Object6",
            },
          ],
        },
      ],
    },
  ];